Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters
  - In Memoriam--Jane Lathrop Stanford, Un-dated; 31; 8x10 inches (Box A1)
    Religious Services- General
  - "In the Next Room", Un-dated; 513-35; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "Inadmissable Evidence", Un-dated; 5127; 14 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Inner Quadrangle Stanford University Palo Alto, California 1891. Shepley Bullfinch Richardson and Abbott Photo by Steve Dunwell 1991., circa 1991; 2004-003 (Box mc--bsmt)
    Possibly a centennial-type publication, but no official SU centennial logo on it. Transferred from Law School archives. C. 1 currently still rolled--in GW403
  - Innovative Academic Courses (FSS, SWOPSI, UGS) [course list] Winter 1986, 2006-033; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Innovative Architecture 95 Spring Lecture Series, 1995 April--May; 129; 17 x 23. 25 inches (Box C8)
  - "Inside North Vietnam", Un-dated; 905-81; 19 x 22 inches (Box A4)
  - Installation Day, Un-dated; 905-22; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Institute of International Relations- "Tokyo Olympiad", 1969; 5163; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Institute of International Relations- Japanese Film Masterpieces, 1968; 5162; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - Institute of International Relations- Propaganda on Film, 1965; 5161; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Intercollegiate Concert: California and Stanford, 1899 Apr 29; 2015-026; 14 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - Intercollegiate Football *** California vs. Stanford Seventh Annual Freshman Game. Saturday, October 27th, 1900., 801-10; 13 x 20 inches (Box B1)
  - International Center- An Evening in China, 1965; 515-2; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - International Center- Arabian Nights, Un-dated; 515-15; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- Brazilian Carnival Dance, 1968; 515-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- China Night, Un-dated; 515-16; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - International Center- China Night, Un-dated; 515-18; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - International Center- Discotheque, 1968; 515-5; 14 x 14 inches (Box B3)
  - International Center- Election Party, 1968; 515-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- I-Center Flick, 1968; 515-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- Indian Dinner, 1968; 515-9; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - International Center- International Festival, 1968; 515-6; 6 x 10 inches (Box A4)
  - International Center- International Festival, 1968; 515-13; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - International Center- Latin American Fiesta, 1945; 515-1; 18 x 24 inches (Box B3)
  - International Center- Organization of African Students at Stanford, Un-dated; 515-17; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- Party, 1968; 515-12; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- Stanford International Festival, 1966; 515-4; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - International Center- TGIF Party, 1968; 515-11; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- The International Festival, 1965; 515-3; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - International Center- Theater Series, Un-dated; 515-19; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Center- Y International Fair, Un-dated; 515-14; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - International Symposium El Modernism a cien anos de "Azul...". Homenaje a Fernando Alegria. Novemer 11 & 12, 1988 Department of Spanish and Portuguese Stanford University, 2005-001; 16.5 x 23.5 inches (Box C4)
  - Invention. An exhibition of books and manuscripts relating to the history of science and technology. January 16 to April 16, 1983. Department of Special Collections. with illustration from De re metallica., 2007-008; 10 x 19 inches (Box C4)
    removed from ASUL records
  - Islamic Studies Workshop. Engendering Islam: Pakistani women, the Politics of Liberal Multiculturalism and Religious Transformations in Diasporic Toronto. Dr. Lalaie Ameeriar. Thursday May 21 [2009], 39815; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - Israel and the Middle East, 1968; 358; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - "It came from SLAC!" (student film by Chris McKenna), 1992; 530-29; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - Jack Cook- A Program in Mime, 1959; 905-1; 11 x 17 inches (Box A4)
  - Jack London: Proletarian or Plutocrat, Exhibition of Jack London Books and Manuscripts, 1965; 2012; 16 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Jacob A. Rus Lectures, Un-dated; 395; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - "James Wobberts, Freshman", 1902-; 513-8; Not listed (Box not specified)
  - "James Wobberts, Freshman" A Three Act Farce., 1902-; 513-7; 7 x 21 in (Box A4)
  - "Jane Returns! in Gaieties '64", 1964; 509-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Japan and the United States. Seminars sponsored by Center for East Asian Studies & others, 1977; 2003-006; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Japan as a Business Society May 14-15, 1976. [Center for East Asian Studies], 2003-007; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Jean Anouilh's "Antigone", 1948; 511-17; 14 x 20 inches (Box C5)
  - Jimmy Baca: "Doing Time, Doing Knowledge", 2013 Sep 8; 2015-006; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford University. Office of the Vice Provost for Undergraduate Education
  - Jing Lyman Lectures, Spring 1990. Lasting Impressions: The Survival of Women's Ideas. Institute for Research on Women and Gender., 2003-004; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Joffre Medal Debate, 1925; 521-4; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - John Barth Lecture, Un-dated; 408; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - John Cowper Powys, 1922; 905-7; 14 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - John L. McNab, Un-dated; 402; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Johnie Scott Reading His Poetry, 1968; 345; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Join the Resistance, 1968; 905-46; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Join the Resistance...at Stanford's White Plaza...Thursday Nov. 14 [1968] with Dave Harris, Peter Ware, & others, 905-46; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Jollification Concert, 1896; 524-2; 10 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Josh is Way Up", 1902-; 514-11; 12 x 19 inches (Box B3)
    Student publications.
  - Judy Grahn Teaches Gertrude Ste inches English 078. Watch for Gertrude Stein Week. [1985 or 1991], 2006-049; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Junior Play: "La Serena", 1907; 501-20; 21x28 inches (Box C7)
  - Jurgen Habermas will speak on "And to Define America, Her Athletic Democracy..." Richard Rory Philosopher and Language-Shaper. A Memorial Lecture, November 2, 2007, 2008-001; 10 x 15.5 inches (Box B2)
  - "Justice" offered by the combined English Club and Masquers Society of Stanford, Un-dated; 5079; 14 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - Karen Meier Reeds, original posters on various student and campus activities: lectures, TMU films, drama, French Party, etc., 1964-1986; 531 (Box 1)
    23 items, boxed and shelved separately
  - King. The Man, the Movement, and Beyond. MLK Week 2003- Stanford University, 1/1/2003-; 2003-001; 25 inches x 25 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Knyght of ye Burning Pestle [probably 1903-], 513-43; 16 x 32 inches (Box C7)
  - "Knyght of ye Burning Pestle", Un-dated; 513-43; 16 x 32 inches (Box not specified)
  - Kuumba African Dan Ensemble. "Sankofa" 2003- Spring Show. Sunday April 27. Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 2006-037; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - KZSU Radio, 1968; 530-22; 3 x 15 inches (Box not specified)
  - KZSU UNDERGROUND 90.1 F.M., 1970; 2008-004; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - La Gran Posada, 1998; 532-04; 14x8.5 (Box A2)
  - "Lady of the Rose", Un-dated; 5048; 14 x 20 inches (Box C7)
    Masquer's Society; Sword and Sandals
  - Latin America, a Hologram. A public lecture by Jorge Volpi, June 5, 2009, 2009-015; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - Latin American Studies Undergraduate Summer Program, 1969; 21; 22 x 14 inches (Box C11)
  - Law School--Admissions Forum, 1965; 2071; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
    Law School
  - Learning Experiment in Japanese, Un-dated; 905-35; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Lecture and Reading of Surrealist Poetry: Sotere Torregian, 1968; 349; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A6)
  - Lecture: The Soviet Union, 1967; 17; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Lectures on French Literature and Culture. Spring 1965, 205-1; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
    French and Italian, Dept. of
  - Lectures on French Literature and Language. Summer 1965, 205-2; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Lectures on French Literature and Society. Autumn 1965, 205-3; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Lectures on French Literature and Society. Winter 1967, 1966; 205-5; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Lectures on French Literature. Summer 1968, 205-6; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Lectures on French Literature. Winter 1966, 205-4; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Leland Stanford's Vina Ranch 1891-1919. History of the Ranch put together by E. Peninou 2001, 2005-004; 23 x 34 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Lewis Mumford's "On the City", Un-dated; 203-13; 12 x 19 inches (Box B1)
  - Liberalization in the Soviet Union, 1968; 18; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Liberation Festival, 1968; 530-5; 8 1/2 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Library Boss Weber Represses anti-war action on the job or off the job. (With note by police officer about finding the sign.), 1971 (March); 90405; 15x22 inches (Box C3)
    Political Activities
  - Literature and Society in Imperial Russia: 1800-1914; a conference at Stanford University 23-24 October 1975, 417; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Loan Exhibition by Stanford Art Club, undated; 34; 12x20 inches (Box B4)
  - "Lock up your Daughters", 1969; 5088; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - "Loves Labours Lost", Un-dated; 511-52; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Lunch at Encina Commons, Un-dated; 36; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Macbeth", Un-dated; 513-69; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "Magic in the Sky", 1957; 903-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - Malcolm Cowley, 1969; 362; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Man Who is Wanted, The, 1911; 110; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Mandolin and Glee Clubs Grand Concert Friday Evening, May 15, University Chapel [1903-?], 524-46; 12 x 9.5 inches (Box A3)
  - Mandolin and Guitar Clubs, 1896; 524-1; 7 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Mao Tse-Tung and Modern China, 1969; 905-75; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - March 4th. Science in Society. Stnaford Memorial Church Afternoon and Evening [1969], 526-06; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - March Fourth Convocation: Science and Society, 1969; 905-23; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Marcus Raskin: "The Military and the University.", 1969; 376; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Maria Bamford: Comedian. Actor. Nice Lady., 2015 Jan 26; 2015-016; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
    The Stanford Storytelling Project
  - Marion Rice Kirkwood Competition: Final Round, Jones vs. Rivers (a case raising a right to counsel issue), 1967; 2072; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Marion Rice Kirkwood Competition: Jordan vs. Weaver, A Case Determining the Constitutionality of Proposition 15 Prohibiting Pay T.V. in California, 1967; 2073; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Celebration Stanford University 2009. The Challenge of His Legacy in the 21st Century., 2009-001; 25 x 19 inches (Box D1)
    Includes list of events from 1/12/09 to 1/30/09
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Birthday Commemoration 1997, 2002-015; 18 x 24 inches (Box C3)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Celebration Week 1998 "Dream the Boldest Dreams", 2002-007; 11 x 17 inches (Box B1)
  - Mary Antin, author of "The Promised Land.", 1899; 305; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Mary O'Donnell and her Dance Company, 1959; 905-3; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - "Mary of Scotland", Un-dated; 511-49; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Mass Meeting, Un-dated; 905-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Materializing Cultures: Science, Technology, and Medicine in Global Context. May 1-2, 1998., 2172; 17.5 x 22.5 inches (Box basement mc)
    Humanities Center
  - Matriculation Sunday, Un-dated; 25; 8x11 inches (Box A1)
  - Matt Kahn A LEGACY OF EXCELLENCE Celebrating 60 years of distinguished teaching at Stanford University. [includes list of presenters], 2010 May 28; 2010-015; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - Matt Kahn: Recent Works, 1974 Sep 16-Oct 26 (Box C6)
  - Mecha Special Fee. An Open Invitation to: MEChA, Undated; 530-36; 11.75 x 18 inches (Box A2)
  - "Medea", 1948; 903-12; 12 x 19 in (Box C10)
  - Meeting of SDS. STANFORD STUDENTS THE WAR--THE ELECTIONS. Speakers David Pugh, Jeff Browning, Steve Weissman, Anne Johnson., 1968 Sep 30; 905-53; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Members of the National Educational Association... (information about free guides etc), Un-dated; 905-13; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - "Memorandum", 1969; 905-72; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Memorial Day at Stanford, 1969; 905-65; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Memorial Day at Stanford / time for turning / Action for the Survival of Humanity / Mem Chu 6 to 6 [poster picked up May 27, 1969], 905-65; 12 x 18 inches (Box B2)
    Hand-made
  - Men's Wester Intercollegiate Fencing Championships and World Game Quals, 1969; 805-9; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - "Milestones", Un-dated; 504-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Minna Von Barnhelm, Un-dated; 905-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Minority Issues in Education (series of lectures), Un-dated; 530-32; 15 x 20 inches (Box C9)
  - "Misalliance", Un-dated; 511-50; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Miscellaneous, Un-dated; 905-34; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Miscellaneous--April Sequoia -Athletic Issue, Un-dated; 805-13; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Miscellaneous--Campus Cyclery, Un-dated; 805-14; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Miscellaneous--Class Games, 1901-; 805-2; 11x14 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Class Gamess, 1900; 805-1; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Miscellaneous--Crew Races, 1962; 805-11; 7x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Grand Athletic Carnival, Un-dated; 805-15; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Interclass Field Day, Un-dated; 805-4; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Miscellaneous--Interclass Field Day, Un-dated; 805-5; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Interclass Field Day, 1904; 805-3; 14x22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Miscellaneous--Liquid Air, 1902-; 905-26; 28x42 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Miscellaneous--Peace Corps -Asia, Un-dated; 905-33; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Miscellaneous--Second Annual Ganes Tournament, 1965; 805-12; 6.5x25 inches (Box not specified)
  - Miscellaneous--Soccer Tournament, 1969; 805-8; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Stanford Karate Club, 1968; 805-6; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Stanford Volleyball Team, 1968; 805-7; 8.5x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Miscellaneous--Stanford Water Polo 1986 Schedule, 805-17 (Box not specified)
  - Miscellaneous--The U.S. and the Third World--Development for Whom?, 1969; 905-68; 8 1/2x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Miscellaneous--Thoropasa Kare Road Rally, 1969; 805-10; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Miscellaneous--Viet Nam--Stay In or Get Out?, 1965; 905-24; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Miscellaneous- Napalm- Legal Action in Redwood City, Un-dated; 905-80; 18 x 24 inches (Box D2)
  - Miscellaneous- Peace Corps -Africa, Un-dated; 905-32; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Miscellaneous- Theta Chi Watermellon Stomp, 1968; 530-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Miscellaneous- Un Soir a Paris, Un-Dated; 905-31; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Miscellaneous-Mecha Special Fee. AN Open Invitation to: MEChA, n.d; 530-36; 11.75x18 (Box A2)
  - Miscellaneous-National Debate on U.S. Vietnam Policy, 1965; 905-25; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Miss Bertha Conde, Un-dated; 394; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - "Monster Bill", 1895; 513-1; 31 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Montalvo presents Stanford U. Chorale ... under direction of Harold C. Schmidt at Montalvo April 24 [1955], 524-19; 17 x 14 inches (Box C5)
    Handwritten sign (17 x 14 inches) stapled to larger board.
  - Mountaineering in Tyrol and Switzerland, 1898; 304; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Mounted image of campus (mostly roofs) with Hoover Tower in the center, museum to the right and Meyer LIbrary to left; trees obscure buildings (possibly taken from Escondido Tower?). Photograph by Lewis Lerman 1989. Bio note on Lerman on reverse., 2006-060; 25.5 x 36 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan, 1991; 532-08; 18x24 (Box C3)
  - Mr. Homer Davenport: The Power of Cartoon, 1904; 311; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Mr. John Mott, 1901-; 306; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Multi-National Corporation: Whose Servance, Whose Master, 1969; 905-71; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Multicultural Springfest, 2013 May 23; 2015-005; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford University. Diversity and Access Office
  - "Murder in the Cathedral" and "Trial by Jury", Un-dated; 505-6; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Music at Stanford, 1966; 202-17; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford, 1966; 202-18; 11 x 10 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford, 1966; 202-20; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford December 1966, 202-22; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford February '67, 1967; 202-25; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford February '67, 1967; 202-26; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford February '68, 1968; 202-30; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford January '67, 1967; 202-24; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at Stanford March '67, 1967; 202-27; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Music At Stanford Spring 1965 (May), 202-13; 11 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - Music At Stanford Spring 1965 (May), 202-14; 11 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at the Museum, 1968; 203-7; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Music at the Museum, 1968; 203-10; 10 x 13 inches (Box A1)
  - Music of Dante's Time / Marilyn Somville soprano and lute / The Renaissance-Baroque Ensemble, George Houle, director. Friday october 8, 1965 [hand-written sign], 524-25; 11 x 15 inches (Box A3)
  - Musical Events on Campus--A Night of Blues-Rock, 1968; 901-8; 8.5x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--A.S.S.U. Concert Series, 1958; 901-62; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Augusta Cottlow, 1903-; 901-24; 11x17 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Bernhard Walther, Un-dated; 901-45; 11x16 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Big Black Jazz Casual, 1968; 901-1; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Borodin Quartet, 1967; 901-9; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Boy-Chorus of Columbis Park Boy's club, 1903-; 901-41; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Boy-Chorus of Columbis Park Boy's Club, 1903-; 901-49; 22x28 inches (Box A4)
    larger copy (901-49 #2) in C9
  - Musical Events on Campus--Byron Janis, 1966; 901-21; 6x13 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Charles Treger, 1966; 901-15; 6x13 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Charles Weidman and Company, 1947; 901-59; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Columbis Park Boy's Club, Un-dated; 901-46; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Concert by ellery's Royal Italian Band, 1905-; 901-32; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Creatore Italian Band, 1905-; 901-44; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--David Bispham, Un-dated; 901-53; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Dr. Ludwig Wullmer, Un-dated; 901-43; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Ellen Beach Yaw, 1896; 901-40; 14x19 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Ellery's Royal Italian Band, Un-dated; 901-29; 11x14 inches (Box not specified)
    5/95 in 341 map case
  - Musical Events on Campus--Ellery's royal Italian Band, Un-dated; 901-30; 22x28 inches (Box not specified)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Ellery's Royal Italian Band. Assembly Hall, Stanfod, Wednesday, November 26th. [Images of Channing Ellery and Cavaliere Emilio Rivela], 1905-; 901-28; 11x14 inches (Box B2)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Erroll Garner, 1957; 901-51; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Fran Schumann-Heinck and Mr. David Bispham, Un-dated; 901-27; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Grand Instrumental and Vocal Concert, Un-dated; 901-38; 11x14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Grand Pianoforte Recital, 1896; 901-31; 9.5x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Henry Mancini, 1965; 901-55; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Indian Musicians, Un-dated; 901-10; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--J.S. Duss, Un-dated; 901-34; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Jacques Thibaud, 1923; 901-20; 11x16 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Jean Langlais, 1967; 901-19; 7x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Joan Baez, 1969; 901-2; 11x17 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Katherine Fisk, Un-dated; 901-35; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Kneckerbocker Concert, 1902-; 901-52; 14x21 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Knickerbocker Concert, 1902-; 901-23; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Knickerbocker Concert Co., 1965; 901-61; 22x28 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Kopta String Quartet, 1904; 901-22; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Leonora Jackson, 1902-; 901-42; 13x20 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Louis Armstrong, 1965; 901-54; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Louis Graveure, Un-dated; 901-26; 14x19 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Mackenzie Gordon, Un-dated; 901-47; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Madame Eugenie Buffet, 1919; 901-39; 12x19 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Madame Schumann-Heinck, 1904; 901-25; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Mormon Tabernacle Choir, 1903-; 901-33; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Pablo Casals, 1919; 901-36; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Ravi Shankar, 1967; 901-50; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Ray Charles, 1969; 901-5; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Raymond Nilsson, 1966; 901-11; 11x17 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Raymond Nilsson, 1967; 901-13; 11x15 inches (Box A4)
    autographed by the musician
  - Musical Events on Campus--Raymond Nilsson, 1967; 901-12; 5.5x8.5 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Richie Havens, 1969; 901-3; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Rudolf Serkin, 1965; 901-63; 6x15 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Russell Oberlin, 1962; 901-56; 14x20 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--S.F. Ballet, Un-dated; 901-6; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Sherwood Eddy, Un-dated; 901-37; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Stanford Concert Series, 1956; 901-64; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Stuttgart chamber orchestra, 1967; 901-18; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--The "Kilties" Band, Un-dated; 901-7; 22x28 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--The New Folk, 1969; 901-4; 5.5x8.5 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--The Oakland Symphony, 1966; 901-17; 6x13 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--The Oakland Symphony Orchestra, 1966; 901-16; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Walden String Quartet, 1961; 901-57; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--Yale Russian Chorus, 1965; 901-58; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Musical Events on Campus--YWCA presents "Nativity", Un-dated; 901-38; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Musical Events on Campus-Ellery's Royal Italian Band, Un-dated; 901-29; 11x14 (Box A2)
  - "My Indian Family", 1945; 511-1; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "My Lady's Ring", 1909; 513-15; 13 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - "My Lady's Ring", 1909; 513-40; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Napalm Rally, Un-dated; 905-79; 18 x 24 inches (Box D2)
  - NaughtSix Presents: Plug Ugly, 1904; 2009-009; 28.5 x 22.5 inches (Box D2)
  - Neil Harris, Two Talks: "Envisioning Authority," "Building Ceremonies: Beginnings and Ends.", 1998; 217-01; 11x17 (Box A1)